Some weeks ago I was browsing on eBay when I stumbled upon this latex boot for just 6€
and I asked myself is it real latex or what's the catch?
The shop is from Poland and they had a huge range of different latex boots and they really looked genuine.
So I gave it a try and added three pairs of these boots to my cart and ordered them.
And this is the package. It arrived a few days ago. Apparently all three pairs of heels are inside.
Let's unpack it.
That's number one.
Okay, last one. The blue
heels and I think
since I'm already wearing the dress, I'll start with a pair of the Orny boots.
Okay, first impression is actually latex.
And I have to ditch my nice and warm and cozy Christmas slippers now and see how I'll get into them.
Luckily they have zippers, so no struggle hopefully.
Oh, and they're on the inside.
They're powdered, so it should be easy to slip them on.
I think I'll ditch the socks too.
and try to get into it without my... what's it called? Shoe level?
Okay, they're really, really long and up high, so I'm putting the dress on top of them.
And let's have a look.
First impression while wearing them, they're not really comfortable.
But I like how they made them and how easy it was to get into them.
If you remember the video with the latex catsuit with the integrated boots, it was such a pain
to get into them.
Now it was really really easy and I can tell you why.
Because they cut open the boot and the actual shoe in the back.
So they were wider and easier to get the foot inside.
So the legs are really wide so that helped too.
They're like a lot too wide here.
You can already see they're slipping down since they're not tight enough.
And while slipping down they show even more wrinkles and it looks even worse with the fit.
So apparently my thighs are too thin on my legs in general.
I would have to get them made to measure probably.
So they actually start being divided here already in the calves.
I love that they have the long zipper and that it's easy to wear them.
I think it's cool to have like a full latex boot.
The shoe itself isn't too big.
So I got size 40 and they fit really good.
But yeah, I wouldn't wear them.
So I think it's really interesting.
The latex is sewn and glued.
So you have actual stitching with threads around the hemline and also around the heels.
So they basically sew the latex to the shoe.
Which you can also see on the inside here.
Looks like the latex itself is molded, especially for the shoe.
And then they glued it on the shoe part and put the sole on top of it.
if you can see what I mean so these are not just random shoes on which they put latex but it is a
whole thought through production here onto the blue heels and what is different here is that
the stitching the thread is white so we have a contrast white and blue and also it kind of looks
like it's thinner than a black one because you can actually see that the
blue is more see-through maybe it's that and yeah these are not as high as the other ones
I got into them really fast because the zipper opens up all the way to the sole
here on the side of the foot which is nice it took me only a few seconds like
with normal shoes and I think they fit a bit better than the black ones. They're
still too wide but it's not as bad and they're also way more comfortable I
guess because the arch of the heel is not as high as with the black ones and
they're also not pointed which I personally prefer anyway and I think I
I don't know why but pointed heels are somehow more uncomfortable.
I paid 45 euro for black ones, the orally ones.
And these were 58 euro.
I don't know why these are cheaper than the other ones.
Because the other ones are definitely like more material.
But yeah, that's what it is.
I kind of like them because they're really comfy.
But when I look in the mirror and I see that they're too big.
that of course spoils the experience here.
They don't smell like the typical latex smell
and as I just unpacked them, probably they're going to lose whatever smell they have with the time.
This is the last pair. It has a plateau, which I'm really looking forward to because this is my kind of shoe usually
and I guess I'll get changed now.
wanted to pair them with latex leggings so to create this kind of smooth transition from heel
to leg I think it works pretty well if they wouldn't have like folded in the hemline of the
heels and soon then it would have been an even better transition because then latex would just
lay on latex also there again teeny tiny bit too white especially when I move the
foot you can see it otherwise I think they're really cool they are comfy they
look cool and they have been the most expensive pair with 62 euro I think
overall the prices are really really reasonable and quality wise you get what
to pay for so they're not 200 euro latex boots but quite affordable I think I'll
definitely keep these because they fit really good the other ones were simply
too wide so I'm not really going to wear them again I guess but these are cool I
also like the look with the leggings and the band t-shirt it's just a simple but
eye-catching look I think especially if the leggings are really tight and shiny
like in this case what do you think of them did you see such shoes already if
you're looking to like upgrade your wardrobe with a pair of real latex
heels then I can say these are quite okay leave a thumbs up subscribe to my
channel let me know in a comment which pair was your favorite and I will see
you in the next video. Bye!